<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Portfolio 2</string>
    <string name="Project_information">Projects</string>
    <string name="Profile_information">Profile</string>
    <string name="Art_information">Artwork</string>
    <string name="Social_information">Social</string>
    <string name="Instruktions_main_page"> Hello and welcome!
This is my portfolio,
By clicking the \"Projects\" button you can view my previous projects i have worked on.
Clicking the \"Artwork\" button will show you some of my designs.
The "Profile\" button will take you a short informatory text about me in both my personal life and professional life.
Lastly you find links to my social accounts by clicking the \"Social\" button. </string>
    <string name="Profile_text">Hello! I am 34 years old and live in Stockholm, where I am currently
        studying application development in KYH College.
        I also have union training as a safety representative and have good knowledge of union and work environment.
        I am a dedicated worker who is happy to take a little longer to learn new tasks and
        to learn correct from the start, I have a easy time getting along with people.</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="Blender_project_text">This is a blender project i did during comunity college. i designed the hammer and the can and created the animation and the interface</string>
    <string name="bmi_information">This is my BMI Calculator which was my first freestanding project in my education a simple layout with inputs for height and weight with a button that runs calculations and a display that shows results.</string>
    <string name="calculator_information">This calculator is the first group project we worked on, we were a team of four and i handled the layout and UI design while my team took care of t he code and the graphic design elements</string>
    <string name="portfolio_information">This is my Portfolio app with functionalities like scrolling, links and a meny at the top. This app showcases my progress.</string>
    <string name="notepad_information">This is my Notepad app that lets you add,save,edit and delete notes on your phone.</string>
    <string name="restaurant_btn">Restaurant Project</string>
    <string name="restaurant_information">This is my Restaurant menu project, you click on a button (starters,maincourse,desert) and the information swaps back and forth depending on what you click.</string>
    <string name="btn_bmi">BMI Project</string>
    <string name="btn_calculator">Calculator Project</string>
    <string name="btn_notepad">Notepad Project</string>
    <string name="btn_portfolio">Portfolio Project</string>
    <string name="btn_blender">Blender project</string>
    <string name="social_list_title">Projektnamn</string>
    <string name="social_list_content">H채r 채r l채nk</string>
    <string name="Profile_title">Profile</string>
    <string name="Project_RV_Title">Projects</string>
    <string name="projekt_info">h채r kommer kort text om projektet visas</string>
    <string name="Projekt_title">Projektnamn</string>

</resources>